Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Photographs 5685 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Photographs
1948- 1974
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union
5685 P
7.11 cubic feet
7.1 linear ft.
Photographs.
Incidental photographs from within the manuscript collection covering major events, labor actions, significant leaders.
7958051
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 16, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, January 28, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5676: International Fur and Leather Workers Union Records 5685: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records 5685 mf: Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union Records on Microfilm 5924: International Fur and Leather Workers Union Additional Records
Joint Board, Fur, Leather & Machine Workers Union
7958051
- Canada - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 1)
- Canada - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 2)
- Children's Activities - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 3)
- Civil Rights - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 4)
- International Convention negatives (Box 192, Folder 5)
- International Convention - negatives (Box 192, Folder 6)
- District One - New England - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 7)
- District One - New England - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 8)
- District One - New England - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 9)
- District One - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 10)
- District One - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 11)
- District One - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 12)
- District One - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 13)
- District One - Photographs (Box 192, Folder 14)
- District II - Eastern Seaboard Leather Workers Photographs (Box 193, Folder 1)
- District II - Eastern Seaboard Leather Workers - Photographs (Box 193, Folder 2)
- District II - Eastern Seaboard Leather Workers - Photographs (Box 193, Folder 3)
- District II - Eastern Seaboard Leather Workers - Photographs (Box 193, Folder 4)
- District II - Eastern Seaboard Leather Workers - Photographs (Box 193, Folder 5)
- District II - Eastern Seaboard Leather Workers - Photographs (Box 193, Folder 6)
- District II - Eastern Seaboard Photographs (Box 193, Folder 7)
- District II - Eastern Seaboard - Photographs (Box 193, Folder 8)
- District II - Eastern Seaboard - Photographs (Box 193, Folder 9)
- District II - Eastern Seaboard - Photographs (Box 193, Folder 10)
- District II - Eastern Seaboard - Photographs (Box 193, Folder 11)
- District III - Upstate New York, Pennsylania, West Virginia Photographs (Box 193, Folder 12)
- District III - Upstate New York, Pennsylania, West Virginia Photographs (Box 193, Folder 13)
- District III - Upstate New York, Pennsylania, West Virginia Photographs (Box 193, Folder 14)
- District III - Upstate New York, Pennsylania, West Virginia - Photographs (Box 193, Folder 15)
- District III Photographs (Box 194, Folder 1)
- District III - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 2)
- District III - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 3)
- District III - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 4)
- District III - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 5)
- District IV Midwest - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 6)
- District IV Midwest - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 7)
- District IV Midwest - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 8)
- District IV Midwest Photographs (Box 194, Folder 9)
- District IV Midwest - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 10)
- District IV Midwest - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 11)
- District IV Midwest - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 12)
- District IV Midwest - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 13)
- District V - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 14)
- Fur Locals Photographs (Box 194, Folder 15)
- Fur Locals - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 16)
- Genocide Panel - Photographs (Box 194, Folder 17)
- Fisherman Photographs (Box 195, Folder 1)
- Fisherman - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 2)
- Fisherman - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 3)
- Fisherman - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 4)
- Fisherman - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 5)
- Fisherman - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 6)
- Fisherman - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 7)
- Fisherman - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 8)
- Fisherman, Manheiden Photographs (Box 195, Folder 9)
- Fisherman, Manheiden - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 10)
- Fisherman, Manheiden - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 11)
- Fisherman, Manheiden - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 12)
- Fisherman, Manheiden - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 13)
- Fisherman, Manheiden - Photographs (Box 195, Folder 14)
- Fisherman - negatives (Box 196, Folder 1)
- Joint Board Officers Photographs (Box 196, Folder 2)
- Joint Board Officers - Photographs (Box 196, Folder 3)
- Joint Board Officers - Photographs (Box 196, Folder 4)
- Joint Board Officers - Photographs (Box 196, Folder 5)
- Joint Board Officers - Photographs (Box 196, Folder 6)
- Joint Board Officers & Org. Photographs (Box 196, Folder 7)
- Joint Board Officers & Org. - Photographs (Box 196, Folder 8)
- Joint Board Officers & Org. - Photographs (Box 196, Folder 9)
- Joint Board Officers & Org. - Photographs (Box 196, Folder 10)
- Joint Board Officers & Org. - Photographs (Box 196, Folder 11)
- Miscellaneous (Box 196, Folder 12)
- Miscellaneous (Box 196, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous (Box 196, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous (Box 196, Folder 15)
- Miscellaneous (Box 197, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous (Box 197, Folder 2)
- Miscellaneous (Box 197, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous (Box 197, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous (Box 197, Folder 5)
- Miscellaneous (Box 197, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Contract Prints (Box 197, Folder 7)
- Armour Leather Companies - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 8)
- Ball, John - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 9)
- Bavacqua, Santo - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 10)
- Brown, Murray Photographs (Box 197, Folder 11)
- Brownstone, Frank Photographs (Box 197, Folder 12)
- Brownstone, Frank - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 13)
- Bruno, Joseph - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 14)
- Bunting, Howard - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 15)
- Burt, Sam Photographs (Box 197, Folder 16)
- Burt, Sam - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 17)
- Cammer - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 18)
- Churka, John Photographs (Box 197, Folder 19)
- Coyle, Steve - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 20)
- DeMellis, John - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 21)
- DeVitorio (leader, Italian C.G.I.L.) - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 22)
- Donahue, Michael (...Leather) - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 23)
- D'Vincenzo, Frank - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 24)
- Feinglass, Abe Photographs (Box 197, Folder 25)
- Feinglass, Abe - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 26)
- Feinglass, Abe - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 27)
- Fish, Donald - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 28)
- Fleming, John (union member, singer) - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 29)
- Foner, Henry - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 30)
- Freedman, Sam - Photographs (Box 197, Folder 31)
- Gold, Ben Photographs (Box 198, Folder 1)
- Gold, Ben - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 2)
- Gold, Ben - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 3)
- Gold-Kleinman Stern - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 4)
- Gold-Lucchi-Tomlinson-Pickman Photographs (Box 198, Folder 5)
- Gold-Lucchi-Tomlinson-Pickman - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 6)
- Goldstein, Harold (International Organizers) - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 7)
- Goldstein, Lew - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 8)
- Green, William - empty house (negative only) (Box 198, Folder 9)
- Grisby, George - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 10)
- Henry, Lyndon (Speaker, head of Fur Dyers Italian Local) - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 11)
- Herbin, Robert - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 12)
- Hudyma, Mike - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 13)
- Kleinman, George - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 14)
- Klig, Meyer - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 15)
- Klig, Meyer - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 16)
- Kurzer, Herb - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 17)
- Langer - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 17a)
- Laws, Pearl - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 18)
- Leibowitz, Irving - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 19)
- Lerner, Ruth - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 20)
- Lerner, Ruth - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 21)
- Logan, Bob - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 22)
- Lucchi, Pete Photographs (Box 198, Folder 23)
- Lucchi, Pete - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 24)
- Marcantonio, Vito - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 25)
- Mierkiewicz, Frank - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 26)
- Mindel, Sam - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 27)
- Morganstern, Joseph - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 28)
- O'Kief, Richard (Leather Workers of NE) - Photographs (Box 198, Folder 29)
- Parr, Phil - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 1)
- Pasquay, James - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 2)
- Pickman, Isadore Photographs (Box 199, Folder 3)
- Pickman, Isadore - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 4)
- Potash, Irving - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 5)
- Recqua, Bob (1st black business agent, Furriers Jt. C.) - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 6)
- Robeson, Paul - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 7)
- Robeson, Paul (20th Convention) - Photographs, 1950 (Box 199, Folder 8)
- Roth, Max - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 9)
- Russel, John (Leader, World Figures) - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 10)
- Schneider, Jack - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 11)
- Shostakovitch, Dmitri - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 12)
- Stern, Irving - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 13)
- Steuben, John - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 14)
- Strauss, Leon - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 15)
- Tomlinson, Gus - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 16)
- Winogradsky, Joseph - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 17)
- Wishert, Jim (Research Director) - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 18)
- Wollis, Bert - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 19)
- Baker, Josephine - Photographs (Box 199, Folder 20)
- 20th Convention IFLWU Photographs, 1950 (Box 199, Folder 21)
- 20th Convention IFLWU Photographs, 1950 (Box 199, Folder 22)
- 20th Convention IFLWU Photographs, 1950 (Box 199, Folder 23)
- 20th Convention IFLWU Photographs, 1950 (Box 199, Folder 24)
- 20th Convention IFLWU Photographs, 1950 (Box 199, Folder 25)
- 20th Convention- Dr. Philip S. Foner, 1950 (Box 199, Folder 26)
- 20th Convention, Joint Board Delegates Photographs, 1950 (Box 199, Folder 27)
- District II Photographs (Box 200, Folder 1)
- District II Photographs (Box 200, Folder 2)
- District II - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 3)
- Endicott Johnson Photographs (Box 200, Folder 4)
- Endicott Johnson - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 5)
- Endicott Johnson - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 6)
- Pictures for Fight-Back Book (Box 200, Folder 7)
- Former Leaders - District 3 - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 8)
- Former Leaders - International (Portland Convention CIO) Photographs, 1949 (Box 200, Folder 9)
- Former Leaders - Joint Board - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 10)
- Former Leaders - Locals 2&3 Photographs (Box 200, Folder 11)
- Former Leaders - Locals 2&3 - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 12)
- Former Leaders - Local 70 - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 13)
- Furriers Joint Council Photographs (Box 200, Folder 14)
- Furriers Joint Council - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 15)
- Furriers Joint Council Leaders - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 16)
- Gangsters faint from loss of blood - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 17)
- GEB Meeting - Atlantic City Photographs, 1951 (Box 200, Folder 18)
- GEB Meeting - White Lake Photographs, 1949-1950 (Box 200, Folder 19)
- Grey, Dr. William H., Jr. - Editor, Afro-American Daily - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 20)
- Gromyko, Andrei - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 21)
- Hughes, Langston - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 22)
- Johnson, Manning - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 23)
- Joint Board Activities Photographs (Box 200, Folder 24)
- Joint Board Activities - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 25)
- Leather Workers - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 26)
- McCarthy, Senator Joseph - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 27)
- Moore, Harry - Photographs (Box 200, Folder 28)
- Reddick, Dr. Lawrence - Photographs (Box 201, Folder 1)
- Strike & Picketting Photographs - Photographs (Box 201, Folder 2)
- Strikes - L&G Strike - Photographs (Box 201, Folder 3)
- Strikes, United Fur Brokers Strike Photographs, 1956 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  Scope and Contents
  January-March
- Taft-Hartley Hearing - Photographs (Box 201, Folder 5)
- White Lake Resort - Photographs (Box 201, Folder 6)
- WWII Activities Photographs (Box 201, Folder 7)
- WWII Leaders Photographs (Box 201, Folder 8)
- Loose Ledger, Cashbook, 1932-1935 (Box 201, Folder 9)
- District One (Box 202, Folder 1)
- Gold, Ben (Box 202, Folder 2)
- District One - New England (Box 202, Folder 3)
- Strikes & Picketing - Selected (Box 202, Folder 4)
  removed from Box 215 of collection 5685
- United - Zucker - Planet, New Years Party, Jan. 3, 1964, F.L.M. Joint Board, Thomms, Newark, N.J. (Box 203, Folder 1)
- Biennial Conference, Joint Board Fur, Leather & machine Workers Union, A.M.C. & B.W. of N. A., AFL-CIO, Hotel Statler-Hilton, May 13, 1961 (Box 203, Folder 2)
- 10th Anniversary Luncheon, Joint Board Fur Dressers & Dyers Union, Hotel Pennsylvania, Feb. 7, 1948 (Box 203, Folder 3)
- Luncheon Honoring 1974 Retired Members of the Furriers Joint Council of New York, Hotel Statler Hilton, October 29, 1974 (Box 203, Folder 4)
- Delegates to the 9th Annual Conference, Joint Board Fur Dressers and Dyers Unions, Hotel Statler, New York, N.Y., February 7, 1953 (Box 203, Folder 5)
- Delegates to the 9th Annual Conference, Joint Board Fur Dressers and Dyers Unions, Hotel Statler, New York, N.Y., February 7, 1953 (Box 203, Folder 6)
- Delegates to the 9th Annual Conference, Joint Board Fur Dressers and Dyers Unions, Hotel Statler, New York, N.Y., February 7, 1953 (Box 203, Folder 7)
- Delegates to the 9th Annual Conference, Joint Board Fur Dressers and Dyers Unions, Hotel Statler, New York, N.Y., February 7, 1953 (Box 203, Folder 8)
- Delegates to the 9th Annual Conference, Joint Board Fur Dressers and Dyers Unions, Hotel Statler, New York, N.Y., February 7, 1953 (Box 203, Folder 9)
- Third Annual Convention, Penna Industrial Union Council, Reading Pa, Apr. 29-30, May 1-2, 1940 (Box 203, Folder 10)
- 3rd Annual Conference, Joint Board, Fur Dressers and Dyers Unions, Hotel Pennsylvania, N.Y. City, Feb. 1, 1947 (Box 203, Folder 11)
- F.L.M., Joint Board Meeting, Hotel Statler Hilton, February 10, 1968 (Box 203, Folder 12)
- Annual Convention, Joint Board, Fur Dressers & Dyers Unions, McAlph Hotel, Feb. 10, 1945 (Box 203, Folder 13)
- Annual Christmas Party, Queen Fur Blending & Dyeing Co. Inc., Pennsylvania Hotel, Dec. 20, 1945 (Box 203, Folder 14)
- Luncheon for 1963 Retired Members of the Furriers Joint council of New York, Hotel Statler -- June 6, 1953 (Box 203, Folder 15)
- Joint Board Fur, Leather & Machine Workers' Unions, A.M.C. E.B. W. of N.A., AFL-CIO, Statler Hotel, NYC, Feb. 22, 1969 (Box 203, Folder 16)
- F.L.M., Joint Board Meeting, Hotel Statler Hilton, February 10, 1968 (Box 203, Folder 17)
- Dinner Federal Bristle and Hair Processing Association, London Terrace, Nov. 14, 1944 (Box 203, Folder 18)
- 1959 Conference, Joint Board Fur Dressers & Dyers Unions, A.M.C. & B.W. of N.A., AFL-CIO, Hotel Astor, New York City, May 23, 1959 (Box 203, Folder 19)
- Luncheon for 1965 Retired Members of the Furriers Joint Council of New York, Hotel Statler Hilton, June 10, 1965 (Box 203, Folder 20)
- Luncheon for 1964 Retired Members of the Furriers Joint Council of New York, June 25, 1964 -- Hotel Statler (Box 203, Folder 21)
- Luncheon for 1965 Retired Members of the Furriers Joint council of New York, Hotel Statler Hilton, June 10, 1965 (Box 203, Folder 22)
- New York City, Feb. 6, 1954 (Box 203, Folder 23)
- New York City, Feb. 6, 1954 (Box 203, Folder 24)
- New York City, Feb. 6, 1954 (Box 203, Folder 25)
- New York City, Feb. 6, 1954 (Box 203, Folder 26)
- New York City, Feb. 6, 1954 (Box 203, Folder 27)
- 10th Anniversary Conference, Joint Board Fur Dressers & Dyers Union, Hotel Pennsylvania, Feb. 7, 1948 (Box 203, Folder 28)
- Luncheon for 1962 Retired Members of the Furriers Joint Council of New York, Hotel Statler, June 7, 1962 (Box 203, Folder 29)
- Luncheon for 1962 Retired Members of the Furriers Joint Council of New York, Hotel Statler, June 7, 1962 (Box 203, Folder 30)
- Luncheon for 1966 Retired Members of the Furriers Joint Council of New York, Hotel Statler Hilton, June 9, 1966 (Box 203, Folder 31)
- Unlabeled photo of a group of men (Box 203, Folder 32)
- Unlabeled photo of a group of men (Box 203, Folder 33)
  duplicate of folder 32
- Unlabeled photo of a group of men (Box 203, Folder 34)
  c.3 of photo in folder 32, 33
- Standard Flashlight Co. Inc., New York City (Box 203, Folder 35)
- Eighteenth Biennial Convention, International Fur and Leather Workers Union, United States and Canada, May 1950, Chelsea Hotel, Atlantic City, N.J. (Box 203, Folder 36)
- Scrapbook Contents (unlabeled) - 1963-1969 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  news clippings -- located in Map case, items too large for a box
- Convention Photos, 1948-1950 (Box 2051OP, Folder 1)
  17th Biennial Convention, International Fur and Leather Workers Union of the United States and Canada, CIO, Steel Pier, Atlantic City, N.J., May 16-22, 1948; Eighteenth Biennial Convention, International Fur and Leather Workers Union, United States and Canada, May 1950, Atlantic City, N.J. -- removed from Mapcase 27 and photos were placed in 1OP, they are too long for panoramic box 203